[{"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Um, coupla' eight balls oughta do us", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Tell me what", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Tell me what", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I think on account of his nose", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "He doesn't have one", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Why? They don't hold him for more than a day or two", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I can't. I've got a kid.  She lives with my parents.  my friend knows where they live", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " No. No way.  These guys catch a whiff and I'm a fucking bag of my friend", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Whata you mean I've got no choice", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "That would be me", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Hell, yes!  What the hell do you expect zapping Mr. my friend with that crackler", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "We all know how much you like hearing that. Okay, my friend, I was wrong. There.  You happy", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No. You know what gets old? Being reminded what a loser you are every time you screw up", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Turns out I'm allergic to stee", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "How far out of town", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't want anything. Why are you so suspicious", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You don't like the tune, find another station", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Therapy session is over", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Highway Patrol", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Said you were a drug addict", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I need my paycheck", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "He knows where I work", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " But you gotta be serious about it", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I want to do this for you.  I want to do something good for a change", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I can't tell you", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I don't trust anybody", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Just some buddies", "docId": "salton_sea.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What the fuck are you gonna do about it, dickhead", "qsentId": 30}]